Here I'm following the cource from Udemy by Maximilian Schwarzmüller: https://www.udemy.com/the-complete-guide-to-angular-2/learn/v4/overview

If in commit history there is message - my solution, and then there is not message - course solution it means that I've done task myself similar to the maximilian variant.

maybe some projects will not have bootstrap after npm install as I can forget to run with --save, in this case run "npm install --save bootstrap"